Jones, Howard Palfrey; Papers apap070
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Work Sheets, Outlines, Undated (Box 57 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 4)
- Word Study, Undated (Box 57 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 5)
- Writer's Bureau, Undated (Box 57 (Howard Palfrey Jones Papers), Folder 6)